Menu

Menu

Privacy Policy
==============

Your privacy is important to us
-------------------------------

At 1happykiddo, it’s our policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website. This Privacy Policy applies to [1happykiddo.com](https://1happykiddo.com/) (hereinafter, “us”, “we”, or “1happykiddo.com”).

We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting personally identifiable information you may provide us through the Website.

We’ve adopted this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) to explain what information may be collected on our website, how we use this information, and under what circumstances we may disclose the information to third parties.

This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect through our website and does not apply to our collection of information from other sources.

This Privacy Policy, together with the Terms of Service posted on our website, set forth the general rules and policies governing your use of our website.

Depending on your activities when visiting our website, you may be required to agree to additional terms of service.

Website visitors
----------------

Like most website operators, 1happykiddo collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request.

1happykiddo’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how our visitors use the website.

From time to time, we may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

1happykiddo also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on https://1happykiddo.com blog posts.

1happykiddo only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below.

Gathering of personally-identifying information
-----------------------------------------------

Certain visitors to our website choose to interact with 1happykiddo in ways that require us to gather personally identifying information.

The amount and type of information that we gather depends on the nature of the interaction.

Security
--------

The security of your personal information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure.

While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

Advertisements
--------------

Ads appearing on our website may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies.

These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer.

This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you.

This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by 1happykiddo and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

Links to external sites
-----------------------

We may share links to external sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site.

Therefore, we strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy and [Terms of Service](https://1happykiddo.com/terms/) of every site you visit.

We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third-party sites, products or services.

Aggregated statistics
---------------------

We may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its website.

1happykiddo may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, we will not disclose your personally-identifying information.

Mediavine programmatic advertising (ver 1.1)
--------------------------------------------

1happykiddo works with Mediavine to manage third-party interest-based advertising appearing on the Website. Mediavine serves content and advertisements when you visit the Website, which may use first and third-party cookies.

A cookie is a small text file which is sent to your computer or mobile device (referred to in this policy as a “device”) by the web server so that a website can remember some information about your browsing activity on the Website.

First party cookies are created by the website that you are visiting. A third-party cookie is frequently used in behavioral advertising and analytics and is created by a domain other than the website you are visiting.

Third-party cookies, tags, pixels, beacons and other similar technologies (collectively, “Tags”) may be placed on the Website to monitor interaction with advertising content and to target and optimize advertising.

Each internet browser has functionality so that you can block both first and third-party cookies and clear your browser’s cache. The “help” feature of the menu bar on most browsers will tell you how to stop accepting new cookies, how to receive notification of new cookies, how to disable existing cookies and how to clear your browser’s cache.

For more information about cookies and how to disable them, you can consult the information at [All About Cookies](https://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/).

Without cookies you may not be able to take full advantage of the 1happykiddo content and features. Please note that rejecting cookies does not mean that you will no longer see ads when you visit our Site.

In the event you opt-out, you will still see non-personalized advertisements on 1happykiddo.

The Website collects the following data using a cookie when serving personalized ads:

* IP Address
* Operating System type
* Operating System version
* Device Type
* Language of the website
* Web browser type
* Email (in hashed form)

Mediavine Partners (companies listed below with whom Mediavine shares data) may also use this data to link to other end user information the partner has independently collected to deliver targeted advertisements.

Mediavine Partners may also separately collect data about end users from other sources, such as advertising IDs or pixels, and link that data to data collected from Mediavine publishers in order to provide interest-based advertising across your online experience, including devices, browsers and apps.

This data includes usage data, cookie information, device information, information about interactions between users and advertisements and websites, geolocation data, traffic data, and information about a visitor’s referral source to a particular website.

Mediavine Partners may also create unique IDs to create audience segments, which are used to provide targeted advertising.

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices to opt-in or opt-out of this data collection, please visit [National Advertising Initiative opt out page](https://thenai.org/opt-out/). You may also visit [Digital Advertising Alliance website](http://optout.aboutads.info/#/) and [Network Advertising Initiative website](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#) to learn more information about interest-based advertising.

You may download the AppChoices app at [Digital Advertising Alliance’s AppChoices app](https://youradchoices.com/appchoices) to opt out in connection with mobile apps, or use the platform controls on your mobile device to opt out.

For specific information about Mediavine Partners, the data each collects and their data collection and privacy policies, please visit [Mediavine Partners](https://www.mediavine.com/ad-partners/).

Affiliate disclosure
--------------------

This site uses affiliate links and does earn a commission from certain links. This does not affect your purchases or the price you may pay.

### We are an Amazon Associates affiliate

We are supported by readers like you, thank you. When you purchase through links on our site, we may earn an affiliate commission.

We’re also a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to Amazon.com.

Also, we make every effort to provide reliable and accurate information in our articles, but this information is provided without warranty.

If you have any doubts, please always consult with your doctor or your baby’s pediatrician before taking action on anything.

Cookies
-------

To enrich and perfect your online experience, we uses “cookies,” similar technologies and services provided by others to display personalized content, appropriate advertising, and store your preferences on your computer.

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. We uses cookies to help us identify and track visitors, their usage of our website, and their website access preferences.

1happykiddo visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using our website, with the drawback that certain features of our website may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

By navigating our website without changing your cookie settings, you hereby acknowledge and agree to our use of cookies.

Privacy policy changes
----------------------

Although most changes are likely to be minor, we may change its Privacy Policy from time to time and at our sole discretion.

We encourage you to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

Search

The 1happykiddo story
---------------------

We're a group of writers, mostly parents, some medically certified, who publish helpful articles for all stages of your child, from preemie, newborn, infant, to toddler. Visit our [about page](https://1happykiddo.com/about/) to learn more.

Categories
----------

Resources
---------

© 2024 1happykiddo. [Terms of Service](https://1happykiddo.com/terms/) & [Privacy Policy](https://1happykiddo.com/privacy/)

Search for:
